

- İstanbul, Turkey 34403
- +905316984759
- ★ thrvoid97@gmail.com

## SUMMARY

I have been developing games for 3 years now and I've made severe improvements during this time. I am considering to move onto more Casual/Pc oriented games. My experience has solely been on mobile games up to now, but I want to learn and add everything that I can to my arsenal of skills. Although I am still perfectly fine developing for mobile platforms for another year if I'm not able to find a good company.

## SKILLS

- Flexible worker
- Multilingual
- Positive attitude
- Team coordination
- Polite and friendly
- Hardworking
- Time management
- Meeting expectations
- Confident
- Problem-solving

# Çağatay Koç

#### **EXPERIENCE**

March 2023 - Current

Unity Game Developer Midpoly Games | Istanbul, Turkey

- Experienced soft-launch/pre-soft launch stages of a game
- Learned a variety of unity packages to help me reduce my development time
- · Learned a bunch of optimization methods for mobile games
- · Started learning Unreal Engine

October 2021 - December 2022

Junior Game Developer Lebleby Games | Samsun, Turkey

- · Have published a couple of products
- · Learned the game development pipeline
- · Worked at all stages of games from development to publishing

July 2021 - August 2021

Intern Pvro Game Academy | Antalva, Turkey

Learned the very basics of game development.

## **EDUCATION**

2021

Diploma of Higher Education | Computer Science

Eskişehir Technical Univercity, Turkey

I have completed my university with a GPA 2.6/4. I have not focused on getting higher grades, I was rather trying to focus on what I would do after graduation, and last year I have decided that it would be Game Development. I think it was the best decision I've made.

## LANGUAGES

Turkish: First Language

English: C2 German: A2
Proficient Elementary

#### PORTFOLIO

https://thrvoid96.github.io/

## LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/%C3 %A7a%C4%9Fatay-ko%C3%A7-45a917202/